<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Smash Handbook</string>
    <color name="mainTheme">#111111</color>
    <color name="white">#FFFFFF</color>
    <string name="t_pp">Perfect Pivoting is the smash 4 equivalent of wavedashing. By dashing in one direction, then immediately flicking the stick in the opposite direction, your character will cover a short amount of ground while still facing the initial direction. Distances vary among characters, with captain falcon having the longest, and puff having the shortest. It\'s usage is more or less the same as wavedashing-to trick the opponent into commiting to something, or to manage your spacing.</string>
    <string name="t_jl"> Jab Locks are similar to jab resets in melee. If your opponent misses a tech, you can hit them with a low knockback move up to three times. If you do the first one within 25 frames, they will be unable to do anything, and will be forced to do a normal get. You can then punish accordingly.</string>
    <string name="t_exdd">Extended dash dancing is very useful for certain characters, namely captain falcon, little mac, and roy. To perform this, you dash in one direction, then at any point during the dash animation, flick the stick again in the same direction QUICKLY and then immediately input a dash in the other direction.</string>
    <string name="t_twoframe">When you grab the ladge, there are two frames of the animation in which you are vulnerable to attacks before gaining ledge invincibility. Certain moves can connect really well during this animation, the most common perhaps being Fox\'s utilt, Little Mac\'s Down Smash, and Sheik\'s Dtilt.</string>
    <string name="t_dashdance">Dash dancing in smash 4 is the same as dash dancing in melee, but much less useful, as all characters can only do this for a very short distance. Only recently has it been used at all. It is good for mindgames, or for tech chases in some situations. To do this, just flick the stick in one directin, then immediately back, and so on. It has to be done very quickly.</string>
    <string name="t_ilgu">Lagless ledge get up is a very underused but useful technique. By landing at the apex of your jump, you can instantly perform any ground attack off the ledge. This is a very difficult technique. To do this, you have to drop off the ledge by pressing back, then 3&#8211;5 frames later, hit forward, then 1&#8211;2 frames later, jump.</string>
    <string name="t_sd">Shield dropping is a technique that allows you to drop through a platform straight out of shield, avoiding the 8 frames of lag that you experience from normally dropping shield. To do this while in shield, you have to press the control stick downward at a medium speed. This is not easy to do, and will take some practice to get the timing right.</string>
    <string name="t_breverse">B reversing is done by using a special move (any move with B), and then immediately afer inputting the move, inputting the direction opposite your momentum. This will abruptly reverse your momentum, which can be very unexpected and useful. This is especially useful for Diddy, Lucario, and Sheik, though almost every character can use it to some extent.</string>
    <string name="t_wavebounce">Wavebouncing is very similar to B reversing - the difference is, you will stay facing the same direction, while reversing your momentum. To do a wavebounce, flick the stick backwards, then press B, then immediately press the control stick forward again. This is essentially the same as doing a RAR B reverse.</string>
    <string name="t_di">DI stands for directional influence and is done by holding your stick in one direction after being hit. Performing this correctly can let you live much longer than with no DI. DI in smash 4 is different than in the other smash games, and there is a specific way to do it. As the corner blastzones are the farthest away, you want to hold toward them. Fox\'s upsmash, for example, will send you away from him, in the direction that he is facing. So you want to DI away from him. To the right in this case. </string>
    <string name="t_wallcling">To perform a wall cling, simply hold toward a wall while in midair. Only 5 characters can perform this - Greninja, Bayonetta, Diddy Kong, Sheik, and Lucario. Wall jumps are the same, except as the name implies, you don\'t remain on the wall for more than a split second. Characters that can wall jump: Diddy, Greninja, Cloud, Lucario, Bayonetta, Sheik, Mario, Toon Link, Samus, Zero Suit Samus, Little Mac, Fox, Falco, Pikachu, Duck Hunt, Captain Falcon, Villager, Wii Fit Trainer, Doctor Mario, Pac-Man, Mega Man, Sonic, Mii Brawler, Mii Gunner, Mewtwo, plus DLC</string>
    <string name="t_ilwj">To do an Instant ledge wall jump, you hold back on the stick to let go of ledge, then immediately smash the stick toward the ledge. This should cause a wall jump. You can continue holding in to get on the stage as some characters.</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="characters">Characters</string>
    <string name="pgr">PGR</string>
    <string name="tech">Tech</string>
    <string name="terms">Terms</string>
    <string name="tierList">Tier List</string>
    <string name="stages">Stages</string>
    <string name="Bayonetta">Bayonetta</string>
    <string name="Bowser">Bowser</string>
    <string name="BowserJr">Bowser Jr</string>
    <string name="CaptainFalcon">Captain Falcon</string>
    <string name="Charizard">Charizard</string>
    <string name= "Cloud">Cloud</string>
    <string name="Corrin">Corrin</string>
    <string name="DarkPit">Dark Pit</string>
    <string name="DiddyKong">Diddy Kong</string>
    <string name="DonkeyKong">Donkey Kong</string>
    <string name="DrMario">Dr. Mario</string>
    <string name= "DuckHunt">Duck Hunt</string>
    <string name="Fox">Fox</string>
    <string name= "Falco">Falco</string>
    <string name= "Ganondorf">Ganondorf</string>
    <string name= "Greninja">Greninja</string>
    <string name= "Ike">Ike</string>
    <string name= "Jigglypuff">Jigglypuff</string>
    <string name="KingDedede">King Dedede</string>
    <string name= "Kirby">Kirby</string>
    <string name= "Link">Link</string>
    <string name= "LittleMac">Little Mac</string>
    <string name= "Lucario">Lucario</string>
    <string name="Lucina">Lucina</string>;
    <string name="Luigi">Luigi</string>
    <string name= "Mario">Mario</string>
    <string name= "Marth">Marth</string>
    <string name= "MegaMan">Mega Man</string>
    <string name= "MetaKnight">Meta Knight</string>
    <string name= "Mewtwo">Mewtwo</string>
    <string name="MiiSwordfighter">Mii Swordfighter</string>
    <string name= "MiiGunner">Mii Gunner</string>
    <string name= "MiiBrawler">Mii Brawler</string>
    <string name= "MrGW">Mr.G&amp;W</string>
    <string name= "Ness">Ness</string>
    <string name= "Olimar">Olimar</string>
    <string name= "PacMan">Pac-Man</string>
    <string name= "Palutena">Palutena</string>
    <string name="Peach">Peach</string>
    <string name="Pikachu">Pikachu</string>
    <string name= "Pit">Pit</string>
    <string name= "ROB">ROB</string>
    <string name= "Robin">Robin</string>
    <string name= "Rosalina">Rosalina</string>
    <string name= "Roy">Roy</string>
    <string name= "Ryu">Ryu</string>
    <string name= "Samus">Samus</string>
    <string name= "Sheik">Sheik</string>
    <string name="Shulk">Shulk</string>
    <string name= "Sonic">Sonic</string>
    <string name="ToonLink">Toon Link</string>
    <string name="Villager">Villager</string>
    <string name="Wario">Wario</string>
    <string name= "WiiFitTrainer">Wii FitTrainer</string>
    <string name= "Yoshi">Yoshi</string>
    <string name="Zelda">Zelda</string>
    <string name= "ZSS">ZSS</string>
    <string name="lc_text">Stage Type: Starter\nLylat Cruise is thhe most polarizing legal stage in smash 4. A majority of people ban it, but some like it. It has a few glitches, and the entire stage leans to one side or the other sometimes, which can make recoveries more difficult.</string>
    <string name="fd_text">Stage Type: Starter\nFinal Destination is the only stage with no platforms. For this reason, some characters thrive here. Diddy, Little Mac, and Sonic are great on FD.</string>
    <string name="bf_text">Stage Type: Starter\nBattlefield is a tri-platform stage, which makes it very good for characters like cloud or fox, who can use the platforms to extend their combos. It also has extremely large blast zones, meaning characters will kill much later than usual. This means that if you want to live for a long time, you would consider going here. For example, Lucario will be more likely to gain max aura by going here.</string>
    <string name="sv_text">Stage Type: Starter\nSmashville is probably the most neutral and well-liked stage. It has one platform that moves across the stage horizontally. It is sometimes called sheikville because sheik can use the platform to carry people off the side for early kills. Bayonetta also does well here, but then again she does well everywhere.</string>
    <string name="dl_text">Stage Type: Counterpick\nDreamland has the same layout as Battlefield, except all blastzones are a bit smaller. The only other real difference is Whispy (the tree), who will occasionally start blowing.</string>
    <string name="tc_text">Stage Type: Starter\nTown and City is the stage with the closest side blastzones, making it very good for characters that kill off the side. Never take a Little Mac to Town and City. It has three platforms which are arranged differently than the other tri-plats.</string>

    <string name= "Battlefield">Battlefield</string>
    <string name= "BReverse">BReverse</string>
    <string name= "DashDance">Dash Dance</string>
    <string name= "DI">Directional Influence</string>
    <string name= "Dreamland">Dreamland</string>
    <string name= "ExDD">Extended Dash Dancing</string>
    <string name= "FinalDestination">Final Destination</string>
    <string name= "ILGU">Lagless Ledge Get-Up</string>
    <string name= "JabLock">Jab Lock</string>
    <string name= "LylatCruise">Lylat Cruise</string>
    <string name= "PerfectPivot">Perfect Pivot</string>
    <string name= "ShieldDrop">Shield Drop</string>
    <string name= "Smashville">Smashville</string>
    <string name= "TermsTemplate">Terms</string>
    <string name= "TownCity">Town City </string>
    <string name= "TwoFerame">Two Frame </string>
    <string name= "WallCling">Wall Cling </string>
    <string name= "WaveBounce">Wave Bounce </string>







</resources>
